

Ing. PETER BURZA

CONTACT DETAILS

peterburza48@gmail.com

+421949104885

Gen. Svobodu 853/31,
Partizánske 958 01, Slovak
Republic

Date of birth: 8.12.1998

ABOUT ME

I'm a graduate of MTF STU with experience as a design engineer, which helped me realize my true passion lies outside mechanical engineering. I'm now pursuing a career as a Front End Developer, driven by curiosity and a commitment to continuous learning. I'm fully prepared to tackle new technologies, challenges, and opportunities that come my way.

My online portfolio: peterburzaportfolio.netlify.app

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript - Advanced
ReactJS, NextJS, Typescript - Skillful
C#, SQL, database - Basic
Unity 3D - Basic
Autodesk Inventor - Advanced
Solid Edge - Advanced

Autodesk Fusion 360 - Advanced

AutoCAD - Advanced

LANGUAGES

Slovak - Proficiency (C2)

English - Upper intermediate (B2)

INTERESTS OR HOBBIES

Programming web apps / games. Playing on musical instrument (violin, guitar, piano).

DRIVING LICENSE

В

WORK EXPERIENCE

DESIGN ENGINEER

Brueckner Slovakia, s.r.o. / Topoľčany, Slovak Republic / NOVEMBER 2023 - CURRENTLY

Assembly Support – Solving complex issues arising during the assembly process of machines for plastic film production. Inspecting and approving assembled machine modules. Creating technical drawings and documentation. Communicating and collaborating within the design engineering team.

DESIGN ENGINEER

SLOVENSKÉ ENERGETICKÉ STROJÁRNE a.s. (skrátene: SES a.s.) / Bratislava, Slovak Republic / OCTOBER 2023 - CURRENTLY

Design, Creation, Processing, and Review of Production Technical Documentation – Collaborating with other members of the design engineering team.

PRODUCTION OPERATOR

MicroStep, spol. s.r.o / Partizánske, Slovak Republic / JUNE 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2022

Operation and Programming of CNC Milling Machine – Writing programs using G-code. Working on projects in CAD/CAM software. Operating a bench drill.

WAREHOUSEMAN

Elektris s.r.o, G-Star Raw (NL), Charlie Works s.r.o (NL), Proplusco s.r.o, DANTEM s.r.o / JANUARY 2018 - MAY 2021

 $\label{lem:condition} \textbf{Order Fulfillment} - \textbf{Handling order picking and packing, issuing invoices}.$

My personal online portfolio, where you can find also a references to my projects:

https://peterburzaportfolio.netlify.app/

EDUCATION

MATERIALS SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

Computer Aided Manufacturing

Slovak University of Technology / Trnava, Slovak Republic / September 2018 - June 2023

Study Overview:

- Manufacturing methods: machining, forming, casting...
- Software: CAD, CAD/CAM, CAQ
- Production control: SIMATIC Step 7 (PLC), Tecnomatix, Witness
- 3D modeling: STL, OBJ, STEP in PowerShape, Fusion 360, SolidWorks, GOM
- Focus: reverse engineering, tool renovation
- Diploma thesis: generative go-kart frame design
- Documentation: technical and technological

SOŠ T. VANSOVEJ 32

Programátor zváračských a obrábacích strojov CNC

Prievidza, Slovak Republic / 2014 - 2018